Guide to the Mattie E. Hewitt & Richard A. Smith Photograph Collection 1919-1961 (bulk 1920-1939) PR 26
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Photographic Prints
  - Detroit Steel Products Co. (various addresses, mainly exteriors), 1928 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 107)
  - DeWilton (Offsite-box 36, Folder 758)
    Larchmont, NY
  - Dighton, Basil (artwork), 1926-1928 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 108)
  - Dillon, Herbert, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 109)
    290 Park Avenue
  - Dodge, Murray W., Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 110)
    1 East End Avenue
  - Douglas, Archibold Mrs. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 760)
    Spuyten, NY
  - Donaldson, John W. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 759)
    "Glencoe", Irvington-on-Hudson, NY
  - Doran, George H., Hon., 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 111)
    271 Madison Avenue
  - Douglas Somerville, Inc., 1931 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 112)
    625 Madison Avenue
  - Douglas, Walter Mrs. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 761)
    "Glenella", Chauncey, NY
  - Douglas, Walter, Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 113)
    1069 Fifth Avenue
  - Dreyfus, Herbert, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 114)
    Fifth Avenue at 58th Street, Savoy-Plaza Hotel
  - Dullmeyer (Offsite-box 36, Folder 762)
  - Dumont, Corinne, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 115)
  - Dunbar, E. Helen (wallpaper), [1925] (Offsite-box 6, Folder 116)
  - Dunn, Edwin D., 1933 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 117)
    1148 Fifth Avenue
  - Dupont, E. W., Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 118)
    33 East 70th Street
  - Duryea, J.T. Mrs. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 763)
  - Dutel, Pierre, 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 119)
    684 Madison Avenue
  - Dwight Manor Apartments, 1928 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 120)
    Englewood, NJ
  - Earley, Ernest H. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 764)
  - Ed Kolbert & Sons, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 121)
    230 West 38th Street
  - Eddison, W.Barton (Offsite-box 36, Folder 765)
  - Ehret, Louis, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 122)
    50 East 77th Street
  - Eighteenth Century Inc., 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 123)
    572 Madison Avenue
  - Elliot, Gilbert, 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 124)
  - Ellis, George A., Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 125-126)
    920 Fifth Avenue
  - Ely, Carl B., Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 127)
    115 East 67th Street
  - Embury, Aymar, 1925 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 128)
    150 East 61st Street
  - Empire Hotel, 1934 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 129)
    Broadway at 63rd Street
  - Engleman, Miss, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 130)
    49 East 29th Street
  - Epstein, Henry, 1936 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 131)
    217 East 62nd Street
  - Erdmann, Martin, 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 132)
    57 East 55th Street
  - Erlanger, Sidney B., 1935 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 133)
  - Errol, Leon, Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 134)
    315 Central Park West
  - Errol, Leon, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 135)
    112 Central Park South
  - Ewin & Ewin, 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 136)
    667 Madison Avenue
  - Fahnestock, William, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 137)
    457 Madison Avenue
  - Falk, Myron S., 1928 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 138)
    126 East 70th Street
  - Farr, H. B. [office], 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 139)
    71 Broadway, Suite 2211
  - Farrell, John T., 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 140)
    Darien, CT
  - Farthing, M. B., Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 141)
    1158 Fifth Avenue
  - Fay, Charles J., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 142)
    9 East 79th Street
  - Fay, William Rodman, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 143)
    176 East 64th Street
  - Ferris, Emery L. Mrs. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 766)
  - Fiegenspan, Edwin, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 144)
    200 Elwood Avenue, Newark, NJ
    See also: Series II, Box 25, Folder 673
  - Fisk, Henry (Offsite-box 36, Folder 767)
  - Florence Reichman Inc., 1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 145)
    16 East 52nd Street
  - Forsch, Carl, 1922 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 146)
    184 East 64th Street
  - Forsyth, A.S. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 768)
    Chappaqua, NY
  - Fountain, H. L., Mrs., 1923 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 147)
    212 West 71st Street
  - Francis, Henry, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 148)
    400 East 49th Street
  - Frank, K. M., undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 149)
    1040 Park Avenue
  - Frankel, Louis, Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 150)
    15 West 81st Street
  - Frankel, William V., Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 151)
  - Franklin Shop, 1927 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 152)
    16 East 53rd Street
  - Frazier, F. W., 1925 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 153)
    620 Park Avenue
  - French, Leigh, 1925 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 154)
    160 East 83rd Street
  - Friede, Donald, 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 155)
    40 East 10th Street
  - Frishmutte, Harriet W. (Sculpture), undated (Offsite-box 7, Folder 156)
  - Fulkerson (Offsite-box 36, Folder 769)
  - Furst, Elizabeth, 1926 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 157)
    42 Park Avenue
  - Gaba, Lester, 1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 158)
    237 East 20th Street
  - Gaeser, Albert (Offsite-box 37, Folder 775)
  - Gaige, Crosby Mrs. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 770)
    Peekskill, NY
  - Gair, M. Elizabeth, 1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 159)
    2 East 70th Street
  - Gardiner, William H., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 160)
    333 East 57th Street
  - Gatjen, John, 1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 161)
    865 First Avenue, Apt. 14A
  - Gause, E.C. Mrs. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 771)
    "The Ark", Pelham Manor, NY
  - Gibson, langhorne (Offsite-box 36, Folder 772)
    Mount Kisco, NY
  - Gibbs School, 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 162)
    247 Park Avenue
  - Gibson, L. F., Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 163)
    1174 Park Avenue
  - Gilmore's Restaurant, 1946 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 164)
    148 East 48th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 25, folder 674
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 165)
    Sixth Avenue and 33rd Street
  - Gladep & Belle Shop, 1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 166)
    485 Madison Avenue
  - Goelet, Robert (Offsite-box 36, Folder 773)
    "Glenmere", Chester, NY
  - Good Housekeeping Magazine, 1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 167)
    Eighth Avenue and 57th Street
  - Gormley, Joseph, 1937 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 168)
  - "Goshen Inn" (Offsite-box 36, Folder 774)
    Goshen, NY
  - Gotham Hotel, 1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 169)
    2 West 55th Street
  - Gould, George J., 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 170)
    Lakewood, NJ
  - Graham, Kenneth, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 171)
    360 East 55th Street
  - Gramercy Park Hotel, 1929 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 172)
    Lexington Avenue and 21st Street
  - Granada Hotel, 1928 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 173)
    Brooklyn, NY
  - Grande Maison de Blanc, undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 174)
    746 Fifth Avenue
  - Grant, Richard, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 175)
    911 Park Avenue
  - Grant's Tea Garden, 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 176)
    See also: Series II, Box 25, folder 675
  - Greenbaum, Fred, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 177)
  - Gregory, Julius, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 178)
  - Greve, Lucius Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 776)
  - Gros, Elsie Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 777)
  - Grosfeld, Albert, 1924, 1934 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 179)
    320 East 47th Street
  - Gude, Edward C. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 778)
    "Mill Farm"
    "Mill Farm", Harrison, NY
  - Gunnison, Foster (Offsite-box 37, Folder 779)
    Ashton Road, Bronxville, NY
  - Guttenberg, S.A. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 780)
    Mount Vernon, NY
  - Haas, John, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 180)
    227 West End Avenue
  - Haggart, Stanley Mills, 1947 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 181)
    211 East 56th Street
  - Haggin, James B., Mrs., 1926 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 182)
    1 East 64th Street
  - Halbren, Harry, 1946 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 183)
    994 Park Avenue
  - Halladay, R. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 781)
    Cresskill, NY
  - Hallett, Dudley W., 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 184)
    Sherman, CT
  - Hamilton, John, 1929 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 185)
    20 East 57th Street
  - Hammacher Schlemmer, 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 186)
    145 East 57th Street
  - Hammond, John Henry (Offsite-box 37, Folder 782)
  - Hammond, John Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 783)
    "Wellwood", Mount Kisco, NY
  - Hampton, Hope, 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 187)
    1145 Park Avenue
    See also: Series II, Boxes 25-26, folders 676-680
  - Harding, Barclay, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 188)
    14 Sutton Place South
  - Harkness, E. S., 1926 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 189)
    1 East 75th Street
  - Harper's Bazaar Magazine, 1929 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 190)
  - Harriman, E.H. Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 784)
    Arden, NY
  - Harriman, Lee, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 191)
    175 East 79th Street
  - Harriman, Oliver, 1921 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 192)
    142 East 55th Street
  - Harriman, R. L., Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 193)
    420 West End Avenue
  - Harris, Albert H., 1927 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 194)
    1 Sutton Place
    See also: Series II, Box 26, Folder 681
  - Hart, Moss, 1941 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 195)
    461 East 57th Street
  - Harte, Renee, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 196)
    19 East 60th Street
  - Hathaway, Stewart Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 785)
  - Hauser Institute Inc., 1930 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 197)
    580 Fifth Avenue
  - Hauser, Emil, 1931, 1938 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 198)
    321 East 63rd Street
  - Havana Post, 1930 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 199)
    10 East 40th Street, Rm. 3810
  - Hayes, Helen (Mrs. Charles MacArthur) (Offsite-box 37, Folder 786)
    "Pretty Penny", Nyack, NY
  - Hayward, William, Mrs., [1920], undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 200-203)
    1051 Fifth Avenue
  - Hazard, Frank, 1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 204)
    160 East 48th Street
  - Hearst, William Randolph, 1929 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 205)
    137 Riverside Drive
    See also: Series II, Box 26, folder 682
  - Heimerdinger, Frederick M., Mrs., 1933 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 206)
    12 East 87th Street
  - Heissenbuttel, Hazel, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 207)
    Bayport, NY
  - Hellman, Marco, 1930 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 208)
    245 East 72nd Street
  - Henderson, Frank C., 1925 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 209)
    1133 Park Avenue
  - Herzog, George, Mrs., 1928-1930 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 210)
    Shop: 780 Madison Avenue
  - Herzog, George, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 211)
    Home: 1065 Lexington Avenue
  - Herzog, George, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 212)
    Model apartment: 414 East 52nd Street
  - Hess, Walter, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 213)
    940 Park Avenue
  - Hewitt, Lucy Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 787)
    "Woodburn", New Windsor, NY
  - Hewitt, Mattie Edwards, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 214)
    29 Beekman Place
  - Hewitt, Mattie Edwards, 1933 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 215)
    The Meurice, 145 West 58th Street
  - Hewitt, Mattie Edwards, 1937 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 216)
    The Salisbury, 123 West 57th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 27, folders 683-686
  - Heyman, Mortimer H. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 788)
    "The Bridges", Bronxville, NY
  - Hilcken, Mabel, 1942 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 217)
  - Hill, Robert C. Mrs (Offsite-box 37, Folder 789)
    "Neiderhurst", Palisade, NY
  - Hirsch, Walter, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 218)
    31 East 72nd Street
  - Hirst, Frederic, 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 219)
    21 East 71st Street
  - Hitchcock, Thomas, Jr., 1930 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 220)
    53 East 66th Street
  - Hjorth, John, Mrs., 1935 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 221)
    1040 Fifth Avenue
  - Hoagland, John A., 1922 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 222)
    126 East 80th Street
  - Hochschild, Walter, 1930 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 223)
    1200 Fifth Avenue
  - Hoffman, J. K., 1943 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 224)
    225 East 57th Street
  - Hoguet, J. P., Dr., 1930 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 225)
    133 East 64th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 27, folder 687
  - Holmes, Christian R., Mrs., 1926 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 226)
    1107 Fifth Avenue
  - Holter, Edwin O. Mrs (Offsite-box 37, Folder 790)
    "Two Pine Farm", Mount Kisco, NY
  - Homer, Lousie Mrs. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 791)
    Lake George, NY
  - Hooper, Harriet, Mrs., 1933 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 227)
    42 East 80th Street
  - Hopkins, George B., Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 228)
    760 Park Avenue
  - Horner, J. W., 1925 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 229)
    525 Park Avenue
  - Hortus Inc. (Floral Displays), 1938-1939 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 230)
  - Hortus Inc., 1939 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 231)
    World's Fair 1939, floral displays
  - Hotel Ambassador, 1945-1957 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 232-233)
    Park Avenue and 51st Street
  - Hotel Astor, 1948-1955 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 234)
    Broadway and 44th Street
  - Hotel Edison, 1931 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 235)
    228 West 47th Street
  - Hotel Lafayette, 1930 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 236)
  - Hotel Montclair, 1931 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 237)
    Lexington Avenue and 49th Street
  - Hotel Pierre, 1941 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 238)
    795 Fifth Avenue
    See also: Series II, Box 28, folders 689-690
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1930 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 239)
    2 East 55th Street
  - Hotel Theresa, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 240)
    Seventh Avenue and 125th Street
  - Hotel Tudor, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 241)
    315 East 41st Street
  - Hotel Tudor, 1958 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 242)
    5 Tudor City Place
  - Hotteling, Warren, 1945 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 243)
  - House of Ideas, 1940 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 244)
    630 Fifth Avenue
    See also: Series II, Box 28, folder 691
  - Howard, George, 1929 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 245)
    430 East 57th Street
  - Howard, Thomas F., 1929 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 246)
    108 East 86th Street
  - Howland, Silas W. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 792)
    "Shadowbrook", Rye, NY
  - Hughes, John C., Jr., Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 247)
    63 East 74th Street
  - Hume, Augustine L., 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 248)
  - Hunt, Clifford, 1930 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 249)
    77 Park Avenue
  - Huston, 1927 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 250)
    1192 Park Avenue
  - Huston, Joseph, 1945 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 251)
    280 Park Avenue
    See also: Series II, BOx 28, folders 692-693
  - Hutchinson, William B. M., 1938 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 252)
    513 East 86th Street
  - Hutty, Warren (Offsite-box 37, Folder 793)
  - Hyman, Robert Bushnell, 1931 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 253)
    520 Madison Avenue
  - India House, 1925 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 254)
    1 Hanover Square
  - International Nickel Co., 1934 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 255)
    Model Kitchen, 67 Wall Street
  - International Nickel Co., 1934 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 256)
    399 Park Avenue
  - Intramural, Inc., 1940 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 257)
    50 Park Avenue
  - Iola Advertising Co., 1935 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 258)
    551 Fifth Avenue
  - Iselin, Ernest (Offsite-box 38, Folder 794)
  - Iselin, Ernest, Mrs., 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 259)
    144 East 65th Street
  - J. C. Demerest & Co., 1928 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 260)
    21 East 67th Street
  - Jackson Co., 1942 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 261)
    655 Park Avenue
  - Jackson, J. A., 1929 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 262)
    60 Gramercy Park North
  - Jaffray, Edward S Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 795)
    Ardsley-on-Hudson, NY
  - James McCreery & Co., 1927-1934 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 263)
    5 West 34th Street [Model Home]
  - Jewett, Maud (sculpture), 1924-1929 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 264)
  - John Scheepers, Inc., 1925-1930 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 265)
    522 Fifth Avenue and flower shows
  - John Scheepers, Inc., 1931-1935 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 266)
    Brookville, NY
    See also: Series II, Box 29, folders 94-697
  - John Wanamaker (firm), 1921-1933 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 267)
    Broadway and 9th Street
  - Johnson, A.H. Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 796)
  - Johnson, E.S. (now Mrs. Stewart Grant) (Offsite-box 38, Folder 797)
  - Johnson, Osa, Mrs., 1944 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 268)
    430 Park Avenue (office)
  - Johnson, Walter, 1931 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 269)
    818 Madison Avenue, shop
  - Johnson, Walter, 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 270)
    509 Madison Avenue, shop
  - Johnson, Walter, 1936 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 271)
    71 Park Avenue, apartment
  - Johnston, John L., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 272)
    625 Park Avenue
  - Jones, Ben, 1931 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 273)
    301 East 21st Street
  - Jones, L.H. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 798)
    West Hurley, NY
  - Joseph, J. Bernard, Mrs., 1935 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 274)
    116 East 68th Street
  - Kahn, Walter, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 275)
    43 East 63rd Street
  - Kaiser, Herbert, Mrs., 1937 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 276)
    885 Park Avenue
  - Katharine House, 1931 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 277)
    118 West 13th Street
  - Katonal, NY (Offsite-box 38, Folder 799)
    "Crosswoods"
  - Kaufmann, George, 1948 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 278)
  - Kaufman, Jerome V. Dr. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 800)
    White Plains, NY
  - Kempshall, Iva, 1931 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 279)
    54 East 57th Street
  - Kerrigan, Arthur, 1930 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 280)
    21 East 87th Street
  - Kiam, Omar, 1930 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 281)
  - Killane, J. L., Miss, 1929 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2828)
    599 Fifth Avenue
    See also: Series II, Box 29, folder 698
  - Kimball, Stewart E., Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 283)
    345 East 57th Street
  - King, Anna M. Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 801)
    Brewster, NY
  - King, Charles Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 802)
  - King, Muriel, 1946 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 284)
    923 Fifth Avenue
  - Kirkman, S. A., Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 285)
    43 East 68th Street, exterior
  - Kiser, Lawrence G., 1942 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 286)
    413 East 58th Street
  - Kiviette, Miss, 1934 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 287)
    400 East 52nd Street
  - Korper, George, Mrs., 1938 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 288)
    17 East 89th Street
  - Koshland, Stephen, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 289)
    20 East 76th Street, The Surrey
  - Lakin, Herbert Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 803)
  - Lambert and Company, 1930 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 290)
    250 Park Avenue
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1922 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 291)
    107 East 70th Street
  - Lamson, F. Vernon (Offsite-box 38, Folder 804)
    Red Hook, NY
  - Lancashire, J. H., Dr., 1925 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 292)
    11 East 69th Street
  - Landisberg, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 293)
  - Larson and Dellman, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 294)
    555 Madison Avenue
  - Lavell, Paul D., undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 295)
  - Lawrence, G.W. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 805)
  - Lee, J.D. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 806)
    Mountain Avenue, Pleasantville, NY
  - Lehman, Arthur, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 296)
    45 East 70th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 29, folder 699
  - Lehman, Harold M. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 807)
    "Willow Pond", Tarrytown, NY
  - Lehman, Herbert, 1927 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 297)
    820 Park Avenue
  - Lehman, Herbert Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 808)
    "Meadow Farms", White Plains, NY
  - Lenox Hill Settlement House, 1930 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 298)
  - Lenox Hill Studio (Needlework), 1926-1928 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 299)
  - Lenygons, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 300)
    1016 Madison Avenue
  - Levy, Richard M., Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 301)
    180 East 79th Street
  - Lewis & Conger, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 302)
    Sixth Avenue and 45th Street
  - Lewis, Madison, 1941 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 303)
    12 East 73rd Street
  - Lewis, Ted, Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 304)
    Central Park West and 72nd Street, Majestic Apartments
  - Lewisohn, Frederick, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 305)
    726 Park Avenue
  - Lexington House, 1940 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 306)
    14 East 47th Street
  - Lichtenstein, Adolph, 1928 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 307)
  - Lichtenstein, Oscar R., 1923 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 308)
    465 West End Avenue
  - Lihme, C. Bai, 1928 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 309)
    950 Fifth Avenue
  - Lippincott, J. Gordon, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 310)
    5 Reynae Crossing, Scarsdale, NY
  - Littwitz (Lace), 1924 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 311)
  - Livermore, Jesse L., 1925 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 312)
    8 West 76th Street
  - Livingston, David H. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 809)
  - Loeb, Otto, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 313)
    976 Fifth Avenue
  - Loewy, Ray, 1935 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 314)
  - Logan, Thomas F. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 810)
    "Our Place", Ardsley-on-the-Hudson, NY
  - Lombardy Hotel, 1941 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 315)
    111 East 56th Street
  - London Terrace, 1930 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 316)
    West 23rd Street
  - Lonsdale, Jane White, 1922 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 317)
    82 MacDougal Street
  - Lonsdale, Jane White, 1927-1932 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 318)
    825 Madison Avenue
  - Lord and Taylor, 1934 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 319)
    Fifth Avenue and 38th Street
  - Lorenson, Laura, 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 320)
    350 West 71st Street
  - Lowenstein, Solomon, Rabbi, 1937 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 321)
    55 East 72nd Street
  - Lubin, Herbert (Offsite-box 38, Folder 811)
  - Luquer, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 322)
    350 East 57th Street
  - Lyman (Offsite-box 38, Folder 812)
  - Lyon, Sarah Miss. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 813)
    Portchester, NY
  - McAdam, Sherry, Jr., 1935 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 323)
    170 East 78th Street
  - McBurney & Underwood, 1925 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 324)
    431 Park Avenue
  - McCall's Magazine, 1931-1934 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 325)
    230 Park Avenue
  - McClelland, Nancy, 1928-1931 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 326)
    15 East 57th Street
  - McCormick, Mildred, 1935 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 327)
    66 East 79th Street
  - MacDougall, Alice Foote, 1925 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 328)
    6 West 46th Street
  - MacDougall, Alice Foote, 1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 253)
    129 Maiden Lane
  - McElroy, Hugh, 1928 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 330)
    435 East 57th Street
  - McFadden, Philip G., Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 331)
    330 Park Avenue
  - McGinley, J. R., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 332)
    521 Park Avenue
  - McGuire, E. J., 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 333)
    530 East 54th Street
  - McLean, Alice, Mrs., 1921 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 334)
    125 East 54th Street
  - McMillan Co., undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 335)
    1136 Fifth Avenue
  - McNeill, Leslie, Miss, 1941 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 336)
    47 Belfast Avenue, Staten Island, NY
  - McNeir, George, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 337)
    720 Park Avenue
  - McNelis, Katherine, 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 338)
    24 Fifth Avenue, Fifth Avenue Hotel
  - Mabon, James B., Jr., 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 339)
    130 East 67th Street
  - Machine and Tool Designing Corp., 1945 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 340)
    200 Madison Avenue
    See also: Series II, Box 29, folder 700
  - Macy, Louise, 1941 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 341)
    127 East 55th Street
  - Macy's & Co., 1924-1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 342)
    Broadway and 34th Street
  - Magee, John, Mrs., 1920 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 343)
    166 East 63rd Street
  - Magee, John Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 814)
  - Mali, J. T. Johnson, 1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 344)
    10 East 93rd Street
  - Manhattan Hotel, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 345)
    Broadway and West 76th Street
  - Manheimer, Dewitt, Mrs., 1933 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 346)
    270 Park Avenue
  - Manning, Eldridge, 1929 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 347)
    14 East 55th Street
  - Manville, H.E. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 815)
  - Marbury, Elizabeth, 1924-1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 348)
    13 Sutton Place
  - Marcus & Co., 1933 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 349)
    671 Fifth Avenue
  - Marcuse, J., Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 350)